Branden Daniel Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in

github.com/BrandenDaniel 😯

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

J 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fire passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautiful spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I've had the privilege to collaborate with a diverse range of clients and businesses. I am currently learning React.js and API integrations.

Work Experience

LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Front-end Web Developer

Sept. 2022 - Present

Melbourne CBD, VIC

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients across Australia.

- Worked on proprietary leasing/salary packaging software for LeasePlus Group
- Management of all LeasePlus group's websites/portals (over 5+)

LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer

Arcadian Digital &

Apr. 2022 - Sept. 2022 Melbourne CBD, VIC

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020 Melbourne CBD. VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian deliver tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes. I worked with extremely talented engineers during my time there.

- · Collaborative work with project managers and lead/senior developers
- · Build and structure WordPress child themes

HTML JavaScript CSS Sass React

· Build and maintian company's own WordPress plugins and themes

Bebble Media &

May. 2018 — Jun. 2019

North Laverton, VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

- · Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- · Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

Tech Stack & Skills

Interests & Hobbies

PHP (WordPress), Sass, jQuery

Kader Boot Co. Ø

CSS, HTML, jQuery

FTEs & Index Funds | Personal Finance | Tech

jQuery Bootstrap Git Azure deployment		Critically Acclaimed Films Youtube	
Work/Projects			
My Web Portfolio <i>&</i> React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS (Sass)	2023	MySalPack (employee portal) <i>&</i> JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap	2023
MySalPack (employer portal) 🔗	2022	Jalna 🔗	2019

Education

Udacity

Spinach &

PHP (WordPress), Sass, jQuery

JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap

Online

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree Oct. 2017 - May 2018

2019

Online

2018

May - Aug. 2017

Melbourne, VIC

Jul. 2016 - Apr. 2017

Team Treehouse

Front End Web Development Track

RMIT University

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology

- Relevant Courses Included: Web Programming
- · User-centered Design